Just like this leaf
is at the mercy of the elements,
likewise, due to exposure,
our skin ages faster than
any other part of our bodies,
but by creating an
invisible protective mantle
to preserve the skin's
natural moisture supply,
Fountain of Youth elixir creams
retard the aging process.
And now you, by joining
the Fountain of Youth family
and becoming elixir
cream sub-distributors,
can share this secret
with your friends,
bring joy into their lives
and put money into your pockets.
I promise that if you apply
our philosophy diligently,
within three months you
will triple your investment...
All right, that's
enough. Cut tape.
What kind of audience
are you gonna put in?
I got that one
from the quiz show.
Too small.
Throw in the one
from the telethon.
What are you doing
about the interview?
I figured we'd keep it simple.
Just you, the chest
of creams and him.
You the actor they
hired to interview me?
Yes, sir. Yes.
What's this "Yes, sir"?
I want you to be tough,
hard-hitting, no punches pulled,
understand?
Think Mike Wallace.
Probe. Make me squirm.
But stick to the script. Got it?
I think so.
Don't think so. Know so.
The more you put me on the
spot, the better I come off...
Would you stop that
fidgeting around?
What kind of
testimonials have you got?
I was going to use
that Dinovsky woman,
but she filed suit when
your cream gave her...
Excuse me. Robert.
You've got some
company in your office.
Who? Jane Barnes, Don Ridgely.
Great. My two favorite people.
Tell them I'll see
them tomorrow.
I already did that. They
wanna see you now.
Remember, give me Mike Wallace.
Stop fidgeting
and get out there!
Watch this.
What is the simple secret
in my book and cassettes,
How to Make a
Fortune in Real Estate?
It's positive mind power,
the ability to
believe in yourself.
Without it, why
ask anyone else to?
And if you call in now and
order this real estate course,
aside from the
book, videocassette,
the audio and a listing
included in the
price, absolutely free,
is this trained staff
of professionals
eagerly standing by,
ready to take your calls
and answer your questions.
You will not be
left out in the cold
to fend for yourself.
I like it. It's got sizzle.
Gonna get you a lot of revenue.
You may recall we had a
conversation six months ago
about renegotiating our deal?
We think it's about time.
Do you? DON: Yes, we do.
Because you've been making a
lot of money off of us around here,
and we're not
getting our fair share.
Let me be blunt.
When I found you, Jane,
you were an aerobics instructor
at a fat farm for $25 a class
and all the alfalfa
sprouts you could eat.
And you were selling
used cars on commission.
No salary. That's old news, Bob.
But it's good to review.
I made you richer
than you ever imagined.
My new aerobics video is the
hottest-selling item you've got.
I don't need you to sell it.
Sell it. Sell it
wherever you want.
Sell it. Go network.
Go syndicated. Go
to Mars if you want.
I believe the exact words
in your contract are that
wherever you sell it in the
known or unknown universe,
I still get my piece.
Now, if there's nothing else,
I have to get ready
to tape my segment.
Who are you? What do you want?
I'm Hal Simpson,
one of your Fountain of
Youth family members.
I need to talk to you.
Maybe you can
tell me about what?
Mr. Ullman, in my
apartment I've got a closet full
of Fountain of Youth
elixir creams and lotions.
Every penny I've got,
$8,000, is invested in it.
And?
I can't sell any of it.
I sense you've lost
faith in the product.
My girlfriend tried
one of your creams
and now she's got a
rash all over her face.
Every road has its obstacles.
You don't understand.
She's angry with me.
She's gonna leave me.
Ken, would you send Tommy
and Billy in here, please?
Son, you must be patient
and most important,
never give up hope.
Remember, lack of confidence
is another way of
saying "designed to fail."
That's the real product we're
selling at Fountain of Youth.
Boys, Mr. Simpson would
like to be shown the way out.
Wait a minute.
You don't care.
You're not gonna give me
my money back, are you?
Thank you, Hal. Stop in anytime.
You're not gonna get
away with this, mister.
I promise you, you're
gonna pay for this, mister...
How did that clown get in here?
I don't know. I was
busy here on the set.
Are we ready? Whenever you are.
Let's do it.
Straighten your tie.
And don't forget: Mike Wallace.
Okay. Everything's perfect.
Let's make history.
Roll tape.
We have speed.
Five, four, three, two,
cue in.
The name is Lawrence Hall.
The show: Straight Scoop,
where tonight I'll be leading
a completely unrehearsed...
Two, zoom back to a two-shot.
With Robert Ullman,
owner and creator of
Fountain of Youth products.
Now, Mr. Ullman, you've made
some extraordinary
claims for this product.
You've said, and I quote,
"It retards the aging
process," end quote.
Come on now, Mr. Ullman,
do you really expect
people to believe that?
I expect nothing,
only the opportunity to
show people that it works.
Just like I saw it work
when I was traveling through
the northernmost Alpine villages.
I noticed the people
there looked strong
and wrinkle-free,
and then I
discovered two things:
They were all twice
as old as I thought,
and they all used the
same natural ingredients
on their skin, the
very ingredients
that are found in Fountain
of Youth elixir creams.
Well, Mr. Ullman,
what are the active ingredients?
I'm afraid that
is a trade secret,
but I will say that
they contain...
I will say that
they contain no...
They contain no
synthetics or chemicals,
are made...
Are...
Are made from com...
Completely nat...
- I... I can't get a pulse.
- Get an ambulance.
He's dead.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Mr. Matlock.
I'm Hal Simpson.
Michelle Thomas. Hi.
I was arrested this morning.
They say I killed Robert Ullman.
I know I-I threatened
Mr. Ullman just before he died,
but I didn't... I...
You didn't do it. No.
You don't believe me.
I know they found the
vial of poison that killed him
at my house, but it's not mine.
I mean, somebody had
to have planted it there.
Down at the courthouse,
they say they call that
damaging evidence.
Well, I'm afraid it is.
Do you think Mr. Matlock
will take me on?
I know he's very expensive,
but I have a little money.
I mean, not much.
It's a car. An '82
worth about $3,000.
I didn't kill anybody.
I'd have a hard
time killing a fly.
And this ring.
I was gonna give
it to my girlfriend,
but I think she's
gonna leave me.
It was my grandmother's.
It's worth about $75,000.
So, what do you think?
So they found monocaine
in Robert Ullman's tea, huh?
Yeah, and a bottle
of it in Hal's house.
What's his last name? Simpson.
He swears he didn't do it.
Oh. What?
I got a hole in my pocket.
Oh.
What? Oh.
I've left my wallet in my...
In your other suit. Yeah.
Could you...? I'll buy.
Charlie, give me
one all the way.
One hot dog coming up.
And for you, Miss Thomas?
Yogurt.
So this fella tried to get
$8,000 from Robert Ullman.
He was tryin' to get
$8,000 back from him.
What I don't understand is
why anybody would pay $8,000
for this Fountain of Youth
elixir cream to start with.
He was a sub-distributor.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He buys a bunch of this stuff
and then he sells
some to some people
and they sell some
to other people,
and finally it goes
down to customers,
and everybody who sells any
has to give a piece of
his profit to the one above.
It's a pyramid scheme.
Hal got sucked in because I
guess people make lots of money.
Yeah, well, I guess
the ones at the top,
and this Robert Ullman
was at the very top.
He must've made a fortune.
Thanks. Thanks.
Mmm.
Good, huh?
Yeah.
My mother always liked hot dogs.
Mm. She used to say,
"Give me a good hot dog over
a bad hamburger any old day."
Hm.
Yogurt, huh? Mm-hm.
It's very good for you.
It has protein,
vitamin A, vitamin C,
riboflavin, thiamine,
niacin, calcium, iron.
Goes into your system
smoothly. It's very good for you.
That's all just fat.
Mm.
Here.
What's that? His
grandmother's ring.
He said to use
it toward our fee.
Yeah?
Said it's worth $75,000.
Hm.
Actually, his grandmother
didn't give him the ring.
She needed some quick
cash from him one time,
so had him hold
the ring for security,
and before she
could pay him back...
She died?
Yeah.
So he kind of kept it.
Mm...
There might be some calcium
and iron and stuff in there.
Are we gonna take this case?
Well, it's an interesting one.
Seventy-five thousand dollars.
That's what he said.
Take off three zeroes.
Seventy-five dollars?
Maybe.
So, what do you think?
Well, on the surface,
I don't think he did it.
Besides, you have to
feel kind of sorry for a guy
who gets swindled by
his own grandmother. Heh.
Natural ingredients
on their skin.
The very ingredients that
have gone into Fountain of Youth
elixir creams. LAWRENCE:
Now, Mr. Ullman,
just what are the
active ingredients?
I'm afraid that's
a trade secret,
but I will say that they
contain no chemicals
or synthetics and
are made... Are...
Are made from
com... Completely...
You think we can
get a copy of that?
Yeah. Sure thing.
Is everything exactly
the way it was that day?
No, uh,
the police locked
everything up after they left
in Mr. Ullman's dressing room.
And where were you
when it happened?
Up here in the booth.
Who was down there?
Jane Barnes and Don
Ridgely were still here,
and, of course, Stephen Spector.
They'd been at a meeting
just before the boss died.
What was that about?
I have no idea.
Hm.
Now, Robert Ullman
owned the studio.
I... I... I know that.
And Stephen Spector
was his right-hand man.
And what was his
relationship with, um...?
What was her name? Jane Barnes?
Yeah.
And, uh... Don Ridgely.
He owned them too, I
guess you could say.
He created their businesses.
Who brought Robert
Ullman the tea?
He made his own. Hot
plate in the dressing room.
Hmm.
A copy of that tape?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, did...? Did, uh, Mr. Ullman
have an office
here in the building?
Right down the hall.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know
anybody was in here.
I'm Ben Matlock,
Hal Simpson's lawyer.
I'm Stephen Spector.
Oh.
You're the new head of
Mr. Ullman's operation here.
You mind if I ask you
a couple of questions?
Sure do.
If you wanna look
through this office,
you can get a warrant.
Good day.
He was nice and
genuinely interested.
He didn't tell me
what he did for a living.
Oh, come on.
You're not that naive.
I'm sorry.
That's not good enough.
What could I do? He
kept asking me questions.
He was hustling me.
Hustled you?
I'm on the brink of
national success.
The video is selling
all over the country.
And you have to tell some
National Informer reporter
that my weight
machines are defective?
Well, they are.
My name is on those machines,
and I stand behind them.
Well, then you're safe
as long as you
don't sit on them.
You're fired.
Pack up your stuff.
Get out of here!
Hi.
I'm Ben Matlock,
Hal Simpson's lawyer.
I figured you might be free.
I just saw your
last visitor leave.
Oh, just a small
personnel problem.
How can I help?
Oh, I understand you had
business dealings
with Robert Ullman.
Oh, more than that. We
were old and good friends.
I got him to stop smoking,
change his diet, give
up all caffeine for good.
Hello?
Yes.
I understand.
Okay.
So you and Robert
Ullman were close.
Uh, Mr. Matlock,
I'm really very busy.
If you'll excuse me.
Well, I thought we
having a nice little...
I really must bring this
conversation to an end.
Who was that on the phone?
Goodbye, Mr. Matlock.
Goodbye.
Can I help you with that?
Oh, thank you.
This is quite an operation.
Tell me about it.
Actually, I was kind of
hoping you could tell me.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, there's a fortune to
be made in today's market.
I love it, love it, love it.
Providing, of course,
you've got a big bundle
to sink into Quick
Opportunity Real Estate.
"Sink" is my middle name.
I'll tell you. Let me just,
uh, suggest a distributorship.
Uh-huh.
If you, uh... If you buy in
on the top rung of the ladder,
you can enjoy the type of
life and benefits that I have.
And if I'm truly successful,
I might even have
furniture in my room.
Sit down, please. Thank you.
Oh, we're in a
transitional stage.
We just moved in.
Mmm. It's quite impressive.
Now, considering
the amount of money
that I'm thinking
about investing
with you in your company,
I feel obligated to ask
about Robert Ullman's death.
What about it?
Well, it places a cloud
over this operation.
Ha-ha-ha. I'm afraid I
don't quite understand.
Well, your relationship
with Bob Ullman
went beyond that cable station.
I mean, he had an ownership
position in your business.
You might even say
he was a... A partner.
What makes you
privy to all of this?
Well... Wait, don't answer that.
I think I know.
I don't think you're
interested in real estate at all.
No, I think you have been hired
to investigate Bob
Ullman's death,
and because he and I
had business dealings,
then I'm a suspect,
right? Well...
I have to terminate this
conversation right now.
But we making such
excellent progress.
I think you'd better leave.
Are you throwing me out?
Yes.
Whoa!
Well, just as long as
we're upfront about it.
How are you doing,
fellas? What you doing?
You work for Mr. Ridgely?
Could be.
Might give him a message.
Hey, wait a minute.
What are guys...? Whoa!
All right, all right, all
right. All right, all right.
Does this stuff work?
How old do I look?
Forty-five.
I'm 62.
Sixty-two?
And you use this?
Absolutely. I use
it every morning.
How old are you?
Thirty-nine.
You wanna try it?
I might.
Good. I'll get you some.
Thank you.
Would you...? Would you
remind Mr. Spector that I'm here?
Ben Matlock.
Of course, Mr. Matlock.
This is outrageous. How
dare you? We're filled.
I'm sorry, but
Mr. Matlock's been waiting.
Uh, okay. I can't
talk to you now.
You'll see a big difference
if you use it regularly.
Oh.
You might really be 39.
You can go in now. Thank you.
Thirty-nine.
Mr. Matlock, I thought
I told you already
I have nothing
more to say to you.
Uh, I know.
Uh, what I don't understand
is why you told Don
Ridgely and Jane Barnes
they didn't have
anything to say to me.
I don't decide for anyone
else, just for myself.
All right. Let's start with you.
Why won't you talk to me?
Mr. Matlock, I'm taking over
Robert Ullman's business.
Why should I?
Okay.
I guess we'll talk in court.
See you then.
Wrong door.
I know.
Hey!
Hey, open the door!
Did you lock me in here?
I don't even know you.
Mr. Matlock, you can't go in.
Mr. Spector, somebody just
locked me in your broom closet.
It was the same person
who was in your office
just before me, and I
wanna know who it was.
There was no one in this office.
I heard him yelling at you,
and I saw the shadow
of his feet under that door.
Ha-ha. I'm afraid
you're imagining things.
Imagine this.
I put you on the stand
and I turn you
every way but loose.
I prove that you had
motive and opportunity
to kill Robert Ullman.
That not only provides my
client with reasonable doubt,
but it hits you where it hurts,
right in the middle
of your rating
at Dun and Bradstreet.
There were a lot of people
with reason to kill Bob.
Who?
Don Ridgely and
another, Jane Barnes.
Why?
Heh-heh. Because Robert Ullman
was taking them to
the cleaners, that's why.
Taking a piece of
their opportunity.
Soaking them at
the studio for airtime.
But now that he's dead,
they are free of his deal.
You don't plan on
leaving town, do you? No.
'Cause I'm coming back.
What the hell are
you doing in my car?
First of all, technically,
this is no longer your car.
It's been repossessed,
which I know
because I just made last
month's payment on your loan.
Now, if you're wondering what
am I doing in your former car,
I'm looking into
a little secret.
I'm finding out why
this is your former car.
I'm finding out why you can
barely make house payments
or furnish your rooms.
Temporary cash flow problem.
It's embarrassing,
but nothing serious.
Very embarrassing for people
whose business is
grossing fortunes.
You see, the truth is
you're going bankrupt
because Robert Ullman was
taking over 50 percent of the gross.
Now, the big secret is
now that Mr. Ullman is dead,
that deal is off.
So the secret is
not only a secret.
It is also a motive for murder.
Okay.
Okay, so I had a motive.
That's all.
Sorry. I don't mean
to disappoint you,
but thanks for
getting my car back.
I didn't say you're
getting the car back.
You're eight payments behind.
See, the payment that I made
was just for the
use of the car today,
and you know those repo guys.
If I don't bring this
car back today,
they will kill me today.
Goodbye.
I've already talked
to Mr. Matlock.
Oh, I know, but now we
have some more questions.
For instance,
now that Robert Ullman is dead,
I guess you don't have
to pay him a royalty
on your hot-selling videotape.
Well, that's
true, but I don't...
And have you
had a lot of lawsuits
over your weight machines?
No. That's a despicable rumor,
and I know which
ex-employee of mine started it.
Cathy Wolfe. We
have her statement.
Here's a copy.
Jane?
Oh, sorry.
Didn't know you had
someone with you.
That's okay.
Ken Pritchard, Michelle, uh,
Thomas, wasn't it?
Yes. We've already met. Yeah.
I was just passing by,
thought I would drop off a
cassette of your new show.
Nice to see you
again, Miss Thomas.
Nice to see you too.
Now, about that vicious rumor.
At last count,
there were 347 suits
filed in federal district court
against machines manufactured
by a company owned by Jane
Barnes and Robert Ullman.
Only R. Ullman was contractually
indemnified from
any liability actions,
which means you, Jane Barnes,
have to pay for those
suits out of your own pocket.
Any other questions?
Well, how angry
did that make you?
We didn't mean to startle you.
We were just, uh...
Just looking around,
doing a little investigating.
With a court order.
Well, don't let me stop you.
You're what we're investigating.
Me?
You're wasting your time.
What were you really
doing at Aerobics Plus?
You saw.
Dropping off a
tape of Jane's show.
This one?
I don't know.
It is the one.
You know it's blank.
Mr. Pritchard,
you're the one who
called Jane Barnes
and told her not to talk to us,
and you're the one
who called Don Ridgely
and told him not to talk to us.
What kind of magic do
you hold over these people?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Just before you
closed that case...
I saw a lot of money.
You're a blackmailer,
aren't you?
You know who
killed Robert Ullman.
Somebody paid you a lot of money
because you know
who killed Robert Ullman.
Talk to me.
If you won't talk to me here,
I'll make you talk
to me in court.
A killer's fate
is in your hands.
Now, you decide who
killed Robert Ullman.
Call in now.
If you think Jane Barnes
killed Robert Ullman,
call this number.
If you think Don Ridgely
killed Robert Ullman,
call this number.
And if you think Stephen Spector
killed Robert Ullman,
call this number.
Your vote will help decide
how this episode should end.
Jot down these numbers.
The lines are open now.
All calls received during
the next seven minutes
will be counted.
You decide who
killed Robert Ullman.
There will be a 50-cent
charge for each call.
NBC's proceeds will
be donated to charity,
and your call will be answered
by recorded announcement.
Children should ask their
parents' permission to call.
Call in and stay tuned
to see who America
believes killed Robert Ullman.
Ben, can you hear me?
Michelle,
I'm in, uh, Robert
Ullman's dressing room.
Did you see me come in?
No, and if this is where
Ken Pritchard was
prior to the murder, he
didn't have a clear view
of Robert Ullman's
dressing room at all.
Do you still think he
really knows who did it?
Yeah, but if somebody
slipped in and out of here
without being seen from
up there and obviously did,
I really don't know how.
Maybe I do know how.
You see this?
Tea. Yeah?
It's herb tea.
You have that copy of
Robert Ullman's last tape?
Yes. Right here.
Put it on.
Okay.
I'll hit play.
Alpine villages.
I noticed the people there
looked strong and beautiful.
Their skin was healthy
and wrinkle-free.
And then I
discovered two things.
They were all...
But I will say that they
contain no chemicals
or synthetics and
are made... Are...
Are made from com...
Completely... Ingre...
Call Ken Pritchard to the stand.
Mr. Pritchard,
you were present
while Robert Ullman
taped his final cable
television show.
Is that correct?
Yes, of course.
And besides yourself
and the other people
who were always there...
Stephen Spector, the cameramen.
Who else was at
the studio that day?
Don Ridgely, Jane Barnes,
and that gentleman there.
Yes, the defendant, of course.
Uh, now, to the best
of your recollection,
did, uh, Mr. Ridgely
and Miss Barnes
often attend the tapings
of Mr. Ullman's shows?
No, hardly ever.
Would you tell the court
why they were there that day?
For a business
meeting with Mr. Ullman.
Do you know what Mr. Ullman's
business relationship was
with Mr. Ridgely
and Miss Barnes?
Not the exact details.
But as the station manager,
you must have sent out
the bills for their studio time.
Yes.
And how would you
characterize Mr. Ullman's rates?
I'd say they were high.
Aha.
Did, uh...? Did Mr. Ridgely
and Miss Barnes
ever complain about their bills?
Yes. What'd they say?
Well, they felt like
they were being robbed.
They felt they could get cheaper
studio time anywhere else.
Were they angry? Yes.
Furious? Yes.
Why didn't they
go someplace else?
I understand that their
contracts with Mr. Ullman
required them to make
their shows with his facilities.
And that's why they were angry.
Yes, very angry.
So, uh... Ahem.
How long had you
known Robert Ullman?
He hired me as station manager
and chief engineer of WULL-TV
about seven years ago.
I've known him that long.
Was it a good relationship?
Excellent. Were you friends?
No. We were business
associates. That's all.
But in those seven years,
you must've noticed, you
know, several idiosyncrasies,
little things about him.
Yes, I suppose.
Yeah, yeah. Did he drink coffee?
Never. Uh, he was
off caffeine completely.
Oh. Tea?
Only herbal tea.
Ah.
Now, Mr. Pritchard,
uh, I show you the
People's Exhibit 7.
Now, this is the
teapot that contained
a lethal dose of the
deadly poison monocaine.
Do you recognize it?
It appears to be the teapot
from Mr. Ullman's dressing room.
It is the teapot. Mm.
And these...
are the regular English
breakfast tea bags
that were found in the pot.
Anything unusual about them?
Uh, they're... They're not
herbal tea bags, are they?
And Mr. Ullman would never
drink regular tea, correct?
No. He would not. Objection.
Calls for speculation.
No foundation.
Your Honor,
Mr. Pritchard has just said
that Mr. Ullman
didn't drink regular tea.
Your Honor, there's a difference
between didn't
drink and wouldn't.
Oh, come on!
Sustained.
Mr. Pritchard, would
you please tell the court
exactly where you were
when Mr. Ullman died.
I was in the director's booth.
So you had a clear view
of the whole set at all times.
Is that right?
Yes, I did. Okay.
Uh, with the court's
permission and, uh, your help,
I'd like to reenact
the final moments
before Mr. Ullman collapsed.
Proceed, Mr. Matlock.
Okay.
Ahem. Now, you're
seated as Mr. Ullman was
when he was answering
questions in that sham interview.
Well, it was like...
In a chair. Yes.
And while he was talking
about Alpine villages
and wrinkle-free skin,
what was he doing?
In accordance with the script,
he was putting his
cream on his own face.
Okay.
Okey-dokey.
Okay, there you go.
Go ahead.
It's okay.
Put the cream on
so we can reenact
those last moments.
Objection, Your Honor.
Is Mr. Matlock serious?
It is hard to see the point
of all this, Mr. Matlock.
It'll become clear in a
moment, Your Honor,
as soon as the witness
puts on the face cream.
Can we go ahead?
Very well. Proceed.
The witness is instructed
to do as he is asked.
I'm not going to put that on.
Why not? Because
I don't want to.
It's because you know
there's a rapidly absorbent,
immediately fatal poison
in that cream, don't you?
I don't know.
And you knew just before
Mr. Ullman started his show
the poisoned cream
was substituted for
the regular cream.
No, I did not.
And so that's how you know
he was murdered. No.
You went to the
killer to blackmail him.
Absolutely not.
And that's what you were doing
with that case full
of money last night.
You have quite an imagination.
Okay.
Okay, let's see if I can
imagine the whole thing.
Objection! Speculation.
Your Honor, I
just said "imagine."
If speculation, uh,
pleases everyone,
may I speculate?
Will it get us anywhere?
Oh, I believe it will. I
think... I know it will.
Very well, then.
Proceed, Mr. Matlock.
Thank you.
Mr. Ullman was a pretty
obsessive person, wasn't he?
He always wanted
everything in the right place.
When things weren't
in the right place,
he'd have a fit, wouldn't he?
I guess so.
And that particular
day, what with the...
The, uh, unpleasant
meeting with, uh,
Mr. Ridgely and Miss Barnes
and my client creating
that ruckus, you...
You tried especially
hard to have everything
just in its right
place, didn't you?
As I always did.
Imagine your surprise
when he walked out
of his dressing room
onto the stage and you looked
and saw the creams
that you had just checked
a few minutes before
were in the wrong place.
You switched 'em back. Whew!
Then you forgot about it...
till Mr. Ullman died,
and then you put it
all together, didn't you?
You knew that he would
never drink regular tea...
Didn't drink... regular tea.
So he wasn't poisoned that way.
You figured out that
during those few minutes
you were in his dressing room
taking care of that
little disturbance
created by my client,
someone used that opportunity
to slip under the
stage, over to the box,
and substitute poisoned cream
for the regular cream.
I... And then you
knew that same person,
after Mr. Ullman
started his show,
slipped into his dressing room
with a teapot full of poison
to implicate my client,
and you decided
to try out your theory
on the three people
who would benefit most
and who were all
present that day:
Stephen Spector, Jane
Barnes, Don Ridgely.
And you promised not to go to
the police with what you knew,
and one of them
gave you that case full of...
What was it?
Fifty-thousand, $100,000?
No, now, none of that is true.
Mr. Pritchard, if I were you,
I would hope that
everyone believes
that that's true,
because if it isn't,
there's only one thing left.
You were the only one
who knew the poison
was in that cream.
So therefore,
you must have
killed Robert Ullman.
I didn't kill anybody.
Perhaps you'd like to
reconsider your testimony,
and tell us who did.
Mr. Pritchard... we're waiting.
If one of those three people
didn't kill Robert
Ullman, then you did.
Now, I don't think you did.
Blackmail is one thing,
but murder is
another altogether.
But the arrow is...
pointing at you.
Look into your mind.
One of those three
brought that
briefcase full of money
to a place you had prearranged,
and there, made the exchange
that bought your silence...
until now.
We are ready, Mr. Pritchard.
Let us look into your mind.
Let us see your memory.
Who is that person,
Mr. Pritchard?
Who did it?
Who killed Robert Ullman?
Jane Barnes.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
Does the state wish to speak?
Yes.
Your Honor, in light of
these new developments,
we would like to entertain
a motion for dismissal.
Bailiff. Motion granted.
Case is dismissed.
Court is adjourned.
Mr. Matlock, I don't
know how to thank you.
Oh, this is Alice
Wierman, my fiancee.
Oh, hello. Hello.
Good to see you.
Oh, nice to meet you.
Thank you so much for
everything you've done for Hal.
Alice has agreed
to take me back.
Oh, well, here's a
wedding present.
But that's your payment.
Oh, I know, but a
priceless heirloom...
My conscience
would never permit it.
Thank you,
Mr. Matlock. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Bye-bye. Bye.
Well, ya... ya just blew $75.
Yeah.
Want to spring for a hot dog?
www.tvsubtitles.net